(Sheldon:)When did we become friends?
(Sheldon:)I.e., I couldn't become Green Lantern...
(Sheldon:)...unless I was chosen
by the Guardians of Oa.
(Sheldon:)Given enough startup capital
and an adequate research facility...
(Sheldon:)...I could be Batman.
- You could be Batman?
- Sure.
[IN DEEP VOICE]
I'm Batman.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
See?
- Hi, guys.
- Hey.
(Sheldon:)- Hi, Penny.
(Leonard:)If you're not doing anything Friday night,
I thought we could go see a movie.
(Penny:)You know, I think I have the dinner shift
on Friday.
- Okay. What about Saturday?
- You know, I'm not sure.
(Penny:)The manager hasn't posted the schedule.
How about I let you know?
- Great.
- Okay.
(Leonard:)So you just let me know when you know.
Okay, so... Oh, God, I am the bad fish.
(Leonard:)- What did I do wrong?
- Why are you asking me?
(Sheldon:)I have no information
about your interactions with Penny...
(Sheldon:)...nor do I have any method
of learning such things.